Interviewer: Did you like school?
Mark: I loved school actually.
Um, I think I preferred senior school more than junior school,
but yeah, um, lots of friends, lots of,
sort of sporting activities and things, so yeah, I loved it.
Interviewer: What were your best and worst subjects?
Mark: My best subject was probably mathematics.
Um, loved mathematics and found I was, sort of, very capable at it, so it was quite easy.
Um, I think it’s one of those things that’s natural.
But, um, worst subject, maybe Latin.
Never very good at languages even though I use them every day now,
but never very, I like languages now, but I hated them at school.
Interviewer: Did you have a favourite or least favourite teacher at school?
Caroline: Um, let me think about that.
Yes, I, um, liked the French teacher.
She was probably my favourite, favourite teacher because, um,
she was French and she taught us to speak with a very good French accent.
Interviewer: Did she inspire you?
Caroline: She did, and I’m still learning French and go,
I live in Australia,
um, and I go to France every year and I go to French language schools.
Interviewer: Do you have a problem making decisions?
What about?
John: It depends what sort of decision it is.
If it’s a sort of instant decision, I make pretty good instant decisions,
but the longer you think about them, then I probably decide,
or try to decipher, which is the best decision.
So, instant decision is a better way for me.
Interviewer: Do you know any twins?
Are they identical?
Alison: Yes, I’m a twin myself.
I have a twin brother.
And my sister has got twin boys.
They’re aged 16 and they’re not identical.
They don’t look very similar and they don’t have similar personalities either.
Interviewer: Who do you think gossips more, men or women? Why?
Kathy: I think stereotypical-, stereotypically people say women gossip more,
um, but I actually think men gossip quite a lot as well.
I think, I think men gossip more in a factual way, whereas women gossip more,
maybe, in more of a personal, emotional way,
so maybe in kind of a nastier way than what men do, I would say.
But I would say that they probably gossip the same, or in a similar way.